(Sheldon:)And yet you get to weigh in.
(Sheldon:)Democracy... it's pretty cool,
isn't it?
I'm not going;
you can't make me.
(Sheldon:)Well, we'll just see about that.
(Penny:)What is the problem?
(Sheldon:)He says he's not coming
(Sheldon:)to the Roommate Agreement
meeting tomorrow.
(Penny:)Well, why the hell did
I memorize the Pledge?
(Leonard:)You have fun.
I will not be attending.
(Sheldon:)Oh, fine.
We don't have to have
(Sheldon:)a Roommate Agreement meeting
if you don't want to.
- Thank you. - Of course,
it will require a vote.
(Sheldon:)Unfortunately, my official gavel
is in my bedroom,
(Sheldon:)but luckily,
I have my travel gavel.
(Leonard:)You're being ridiculous.
(Sheldon:)There's a motion on the floor,
"I'm ridiculous."
(Sheldon:)Do we have a second?
(Sheldon:)Hmm? Hmm?
There is no second.
(Sheldon:)The motion is denied.
(Sheldon:)Next time, make sure
you have the votes first.
(Sheldon:)That was embarrassing.
(Leonard:)Can you please
talk to him?
(Penny:)Well, why are you
fighting him on this?
(Leonard:)Because I am tired of him
always getting his way.
(Leonard:)We don't need a stupid meeting.
(Leonard:)We don't even need
a Roommate Agreement,
(Leonard:)and I hope that sandwich
does cause a party!
(Penny:)Well, I will still
come to your meeting.